Ganga Chetan Mahajan

B-103, Highlife Housing Society, Sun city Road, Anandnagar Sihngad Road Pune 411051 Cell No. +91 7798389955 Email: gangachavan15@gmail.com

Master & Graduation in commerce, with 12 + years of experience in Accounting, Auditing, Taxation.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Since January 2012 working with **Deep and Deep Industries** as an **Account Executive** (Financial Reporting, Accounting & Reconciliations, Audit, Direct & Indirect Taxations & MIS.

Sep 2010 to Dec 2012 –Worked with **Manohar Shetty and Company** as an **Accountant and Audit Assistant**

(Finalization of Accounts and Financial Statements, Taxation and Audit)

QUALIFICATIONS

- Masters in Commerce (M.Com) from Pune University, Pune- Specialization in Costing (Year 2012)
- > Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com) from Pune University, Pune- Specialization in Costing (Year 2010)
- DCA (Diploma in Computer Application)
- > MSCIT
- > Tally ERP 9

SKILLS/KNOWLEDGE

- Statutory Reporting, Financial Reporting, MIS.
- Accounting & financial knowledge with exposure to Financial Analysis, Accounting & Reconciliation.
- Internal Audit, Statutory Audits and Knowledge of Direct and Indirect Taxation.
- > Team Player, Assertive, Proactive attitude, Attentive, Quick learner and ready to explore new domains.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

1) Deep and Deep Industries (Accountant)

(Water Fountain and Industrial Nozzles Manufacturing Industries) Working Period: January 2012 to Present

- Daily Cash and Banking Transaction.
- > TDS & GST Working
- ➤ Handing Import & Export Transaction and documentation
- Liaisoning with banks and financial institutions for obtaining loans, Cash credit Facility, Bank Guarantee etc.
- Active participation in finalization of accounts and responsible for meeting auditing requirement by providing necessary information.
- Handling Cash management
- > Salary Processing
- Preparing Invoices
- Responsible for Data accuracy
- > Responsible for all payments i.e. Vendor Payment, Advance Settlement
- ➤ Handling all tax payments, tax returns and tax audits for the company.
- > Follow-up of Recovery department for outstanding debtors reconciliation
- > Preparing all documents for loan Proposals
- Preparing summary for all sites
- > Team Management

2) Manohar Shetty and Company (Accountant and Audit Assistant)

(Chartered Accountant Firm) Working Period: September 2010 to December 2012

- Booking of Expenses/ Data Entry
- Finalization of Accounts and Preparing Financial Statements viz. Balance Sheet and P&L Accounts.
- > Day to day Entry, Sales, Purchase, Cash, Bank and Bank Reconciliation.
- > TDS Working
- Service Tax Working
- VAT Filling
- > Non-Profit Organization Audit
- Monthly MIS

Certifications

- Tally
- ICA (Industrial Certified Accountant)
- MSCIT
- Advance Excel

EXTRA- CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Reading Books
- Exploring New Places

PERSONAL DOSSIER

Name :- Ganga Chetan Mahajan Date of Birth: 15th August 1989

Marital Status: Married.

Language Proficiency: English, Marathi, Hindi

Gender : Female **Nationality:** Indian

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all information given above is correct and true to best of my knowledge.

Date:

Place: Pune

(Ganga Chetan Mahajan)